<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gateway Boot Error on WATERCOLOR.WHISTLER.PAGE</title><link>https://watercolor.whistler.page/</link><description>Recent content in Gateway Boot Error on WATERCOLOR.WHISTLER.PAGE</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://watercolor.whistler.page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Average Tuesday</title><link>https://watercolor.whistler.page/post/average-tuesday/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://watercolor.whistler.page/post/average-tuesday/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve really been slacking on this commission for a while, but it&amp;rsquo;s finally done! Been really hard getting over the roadblock of anxiety of writing other people&amp;rsquo;s characters, but I&amp;rsquo;d say I did a half decent job! Still debating if I want to post this anywhere else or not, though&amp;hellip;
This story details my boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s OC getting constantly stepped on and squished in various ways, during the events of an Average Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Debug Mode</title><link>https://watercolor.whistler.page/post/debug-mode/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 01:34:17 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://watercolor.whistler.page/post/debug-mode/</guid><description>Hey look, it&amp;rsquo;s my first commission! This one&amp;rsquo;s rather simple, but it let me try out some new formatting styles. I really like how it ended up, even if it&amp;rsquo;s not truly 1:1 with the original game. What I&amp;rsquo;m more proud of is the dialogue, especially considering how much of a stickler I am when it comes to being accurate to the source material.
Commissioner is anonymous, the anon is over 18.</description></item><item><title>Commission Manual</title><link>https://watercolor.whistler.page/comm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 02:02:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://watercolor.whistler.page/comm/</guid><description>COMMISSION STATUS: CLOSED CURRENTLY HANDLING: 1/2 Hello. If you have any questions, or are ready to commission, please ask on Discord. wistlyr#6900
Forewarning: I may decide not to do a commission at any point. You will be refunded if you already paid.
For 0-2k word stories, I charge $20. For 2-3k word stories, I charge $30. For 3-5k word stories, I charge $40. For 5k+ word stories, I charge $50. If an OC is included, an extra $10 is added, with $5 for each subsequent OC.</description></item><item><title>Self Cauterization</title><link>https://watercolor.whistler.page/post/self-cauterization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 01:11:17 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://watercolor.whistler.page/post/self-cauterization/</guid><description>This is the second example of what I can do. I specifically wrote it to be a little shorter than the first one I did. The story is based on my OC, Illumi #### (an Octoling), but feel free to substitute whoever in there, that&amp;rsquo;s why the name is struck out. It&amp;rsquo;s irrelevant anyway for a drone, no? 121 has an actual name too, but its not important.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had the idea in the back of my head for an office hallway liminal space drowning sequence as how someone gets sanitized &amp;ldquo;mentally&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Frozen Welcomes</title><link>https://watercolor.whistler.page/post/frozen-welcomes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 22:11:24 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://watercolor.whistler.page/post/frozen-welcomes/</guid><description>I made this both as an example of what I&amp;rsquo;m capable of, as well as to fill a woefully underfilled niche: Froslass content. I love ghost types. Froslass is my favorite ghost type. I really needn&amp;rsquo;t say more.
That said, a content warning for abuse is here. Other than that, mild TF content.
[ Download PDF ] | [ Read Online ] | [ View on fA ]</description></item><item><title/><link>https://watercolor.whistler.page/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://watercolor.whistler.page/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Display Properties</title><link>https://watercolor.whistler.page/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://watercolor.whistler.page/about/</guid><description>Checking file system on C: The type of the file system is NTFS. One of your disks needs to be checked for consistency. You may cancel the disk check, but it is strongly recommended that you continue. To skip disk checking, press any key within 10 second(s). About Watercolor Hello.
I write NSFW works under the name wtrclr here. You have to be 18+ to read them.
I will write pretty much anything.</description></item></channel></rss>